[LC] cessna zero romeo alpha runway three zero right cleared for the option
[N160RA] three zero right cleared for the option zero romeo alpha
[N160RA] i believe you gave us the clearance in the upwind but thank you for confirming
[LC] I did.  I was just verifying. yep
[N160RA] Better safe than sorry, they say
[LC] one through five okay for local one local two local assist three zero left three zero right two five
[LC] traffic is metro two on taxiway papa doing pattern work.
[N786TX] las vegas tower cirrus seven eight six tango xray holding short three zero left kilo ready for departure.
[LC] that's their first call.
[LC] cirrus seven eight six tango xray north las vegas tower left turn approved runway three zero left cleared for takeoff.
[N786TX] three zero left kilo cleared for takeoff six tango xray
[LC] okay, so they're going to forty inbound is airsmart five five not on frequency or scope yet
[LC] proposed inbound is meridian seven charlie xray
[LC] I don't think I said it but cessna zero romeo alpha in the upwind
[LC] not cleared for a three zero right pattern work light sport in the run-up area
[METRO2] (unintelligible) metro two (unintelligible) taxiway papa would like to air taxi over to the uh metro pad
[LC] metro two uh proceed uh direct to the metro pad
[METRO2] metro two
[LC] six tango xray contact las vegas departure
[N768TX] over to las vegas departure six tango xray
[LC] cessna zero romeo alpha runway three zero right cleared for the option
[N160RA] three zero right cleared for the option zero romeo alpha
[XSM55] north las vegas tower airsmart five five visual runway three zero left
[LC] airsmart five five north las vegas tower continue left traffic runway three zero left
[XSM55] continue left traffic for three zero left airsmart five five
[XSM55] and tower airsmart five five would you prefer us to overfly the field at or above thirty five or pass the departure end
[LC] airsmart five five over the field at three thousand five hundred
[XSM55] airsmart five five
[LC] airsmart five five runway three zero left clear to land
[XSM55] cleared to land runway three zero left airsmart five five
[N90MX] tower nine zero mike xray holding short of three zero left at kilo
[LC] light sport nine zero mike xray north las vegas tower no delay runway three zero left cleared for takeoff wind calm
[N90MX] no delay three zero left nine zero mike xray
[LC] cessna zero romeo alpha runway three zero right cleared for the option
[N160RA] three zero right cleared for the option zero romeo alpha
[LC] airsmart five five taxi charlie to parking
[XSM55] taxi charlie parking airsmart five five
[LC] nellis north las vegas air smart five five on the ground ez
[NATCF] uh two five miles to fly november nine seven charlie xray visual approach full stop
[LC] runway three zero left
[NATCF] g g
[N160RA] tower zero romeo alpha would like to request a short approach on this one please
[LC] cessna zero romeo alpha short approach approved three zero right cleared for the option
[N160RA] short approach approved three zero right cleared for the option zero romeo alpha
[N97CX] north las vegas tower november nine seven charlie xray is descending out of seven thousand six hundred for landing on three zero left and uh nellis said to cross midfield
[UNKNOWN] (unintelligible) Carol
[N97CX] hi
[UNKNOWN] where you go where you coming from
[LC] nine seven charlie xray north Las Vegas tower continue runway three zero left
[N97CX] okay continue for runway three zero left nine seven charlie x-ray we'll cross midfield
[LC] wind three one zero seven
[N97CX] thank you for the winds three one zero seven got it
[N738CY] north las vegas tower cessna three eight charlie yankee over red rock uh casino with information november looking for full stop terminate
[LC] cessna seven three eight charlie yankee north las vegas tower enter midfield left downwind runway three zero left
[N738CY] midfield left downwind runway three zero left eight charlie yankee
[N466MD] north las vegas tower extra four six six mike delta Ione mountain november full stop
[LC] extra four six six mike delta north las vegas tower make left traffic runway three zero left
[N466MD] left traffic runway three zero left six mike delta
[N160RA] tower zero romeo alpha would like to request another short approach please
[LC] cessna zero romeo alpha short approach approved runway three zero right cleared for the option
[N160RA] short approach approved three zero right cleared for the option zero romeo alpha
[LC] cessna eight charlie yankee amend instructions turn left towards lone mountain i'll call you back in
[N738CY] left turn lone mountain eight charlie yankee
[LC] extra six mike delta reduce speed you'll be following a meridian overflying the field at midfield now report in sight
[N466MD] we'Il reduce speed six mike delta looking for em
[LC] cessna eight charlie yankee you can begin a right turn back in to the enter a right downwind runway three zero right
[N738CY] entering a right downwind three zero right eight charlie yankee
[LC] november seven charlie xray runway three zero left cleared to land
[N97CX] three zero left cleared to land nine seven charlie xray
[N466MD] traffic in sight six mike delta
[LC] extra six mike delta number two runway three zero left cleared to land
[N466MD] number two runway three zero left cleared to land six mike delta
[LC] seven charlie xray i think i said it right runway three zero Ieft seven charlie xray runway three zero left
[N97CX] yeah affirmative three zero left that's what i heard nine seven charlie xray
[UNKNOWN] (unintelligible)
[N455MD] do you want six mike delta to three sixty
[LC] november six mike delta you can come on to land you can land you can still land if you're fine
[N456MD] six mike delta
[LC] elght charlie yankee you're number two to follow that traffic runway three zero left cleared to land
[N73BCY] two three zero cleared to land eight charlie yankee